krop.com 2017-03-27

# Krop

Welcome to our website. We are Krop and its affiliates (hereafter "Krop," or "Site," or "Website," or "our," or "we") 

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. We respect your (hereafter "You" "User" or "Account(s)") privacy and are committed to protecting any personal information you share with us through this website. This privacy policy statement ("Privacy Policy") explains how Krop collects, uses, and discloses information on users of the Site. 

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect information from you when you register on our site. When registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

## WHAT WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  1. To personalize your experience;
  2. to improve our website;
  3. to improve customer service;
  4. to administer promotions, surveys, or other site feature;
  5. to send periodic emails; and
  6. the email address you provide, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your account. 

## HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

## DO WE USE COOKIES?

Yes.

## DO WE DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

## THIRD PARTY LINKS

We may include or offer third party services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

## CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. Therefore, pursuant to the Online Privacy Protection Act of 2003, California Business and Professions Code §§ 22575-22579, we will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

## CHILDRENS’ ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act); we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

## ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY ONLY

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

## YOUR CONSENT

By using our site, you consent to and agree with our web site privacy policy. 

## CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

## THIS POLICY WAS LAST MODIFIED ON:

This policy was last modified on March 24, 2016. 

## CONTACTING US

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at [support@krop.com](mailto:support@krop.com)
